我們可以去車上待著...
We could jump in the car if...
在這兒等著
We'll wait.
-你給議員買生日禮物了嗎  -沒有
- Did you get the congressman anything for his birthday? - No.
我買了袖扣  銀質的  有他的...
I got him cufflinks. Silver, with his --
我們不談論生日  不送禮物
We don't talk about birthdays. We don't do gifts.
為什麼
Why not?
去把袖扣退了吧
You should return the cufflinks.
道格
Doug?
我一直在給你打電話
Tried calling you.
-我把手機留在...  -我們得談談
- I left my phone in the... - We need to talk.
怎麼了
What's going on?
克裏斯蒂娜  我剛剛跟她談過
Christina. I just spoke to her.
佐伊...
Did Zoe...?
是的  但還不止
Yeah. But that's not all.
他們還找到了瑞秋
They tracked down Rachel, too.
弗蘭西斯
Francis?
跟我說說瑞秋  她在哪
Tell me about Rachel. Where is she?
我控制住她了
I have her under control.
答非所問
That's not what I asked.
我送她回家了  不用擔心她
I drove her home. We don't have to worry about her.
你當初也這麼說斯克斯基女士
You said the same about Ms. Skorsky.
還有別人嗎
Anyone else involved?
只有簡寧和佐伊
Just Janine and Zoe.
他們在查羅素酒駕的事
They asked about Russo's arrest
而且知道他去找過科佩尼科
and they know he went to see Kapeniak.
我想他們應該就知道這些了
I assume that's as far as they've gotten.
不要想當然
Assume nothing.
我去告訴巴尼·豪爾
I'll alert Barney Hull.
拿佐伊怎麼辦
What do you want me to do about Zoe?
我對付佐伊
I'll handle Zoe.
你去辦事吧
Get to work.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我拿走了
I emptied it.
你週二就又老一歲了
You're another year older on Tuesday.
副總統可不能抽煙
And we can't have a vice president who smokes.
你能結束嗎
Can you finish?
什麼
What?
我完事了
I'm good.
你怎麼了
What's wrong?
沒什麼  就是完事了
Nothing. I just said finish.
我不想...如果你不想...
Well, I don't want just -- if you're not...
好吧  隨便了
Okay, fine. Whatever.
佐伊  是我做錯了什麼嗎
Zoe, did I do something that made you...?
沒有
No.
佐伊  你不能說一句完事了  然後就停下啊
Zoe, you can't say something like "just finish" and then shut down.
這裏很安全  佐伊  我不是他
This is safe, Zoe. I'm not him.
早上好  傑姬
Good morning, Jackie.
早上好
Good morning.
理查德·拉塞爾
Richard Russell.
長期反對民權運動
1963年  《民權法案》
Civil Rights Act. 1963.
不是所有人都能留下美名
Not everyone can be on the right side of history.
連林登也曾站錯隊
No, not even Lyndon for a time,
但沒有拉塞爾  林登也當不上多數黨領袖
but he would have never become majority leader without him.
但是沒有約翰遜參議院大樓
Well, there's no Johnson Senate building.
有拉塞爾參議院大樓
是啊  只能委屈他拿一棟總統圖書館湊合了
No. He had to settle for a presidential library.
我們都好久沒機會聊聊了
So it's been some time since you and I have had a chance to catch up.
你的工作做得很出色  傑姬
You've been an outstanding deputy, Jackie.
比你那些老練的同事還高效
Far more effective than your more seasoned colleagues.
你能建立同盟  必要時還有股狠勁
You're a coalition builder, a fighter when you have to be.
告訴我  你怎麼看自己的前途
Tell me, where do you see yourself headed?
我想做眾議院軍事委員會主席
I'd like to aim for the chair of Armed Services.
或者眾議院國土安全委員會主席
Or Homeland Security.
你考慮過進入領導層嗎
Have you ever considered serving in the leadership?
我想那至少也得等八...十年了
I figure that might be possible eight, ten years from now.
如果我說你這一屆就能進入領導層呢
Well, what if I suggested that you could serve in leadership this term.
接替我  做黨鞭
To replace me. As whip.
你要接任副總統了
You're being tapped for VP.
就算是這樣吧
Let's assume that's true.
-這也說得通  但我做黨鞭  -是的
- Well, that makes sense. But me as whip? - Yes.
我只是個第三任女議員
A third-term congresswoman?
你的能力有目共睹  而且還參過戰
A universally admired incumbent who also happens to be a war veteran.
按順序也該是韋伯  或巴克沃特
Webb is next in line. Or Buchwalter.
所以  你想想這意味著什麼
So just consider that for a moment.
他們會牽制彼此的選票
They'll draw votes from one another.
我可沒說你會贏得很輕鬆
Oh, I'm not saying you wouldn't have to fight for it,
但我願意幫你
but I'd be willing to give you the ammunition.
過來
Come over here.
這是什麼
What is this?
我關於韋伯和巴克沃特的文件
My files on Webb and Buchwalter.
你自己看看吧
Why don't you take a look?
我們過幾天再談
We'll speak in a few days.
還有一個關於你的文件夾
Oh, and, uh, there's one on you.
或許你會想先讀那個
You might want to begin by reading that one first.
簡寧怎麼說
What'd Janine say?
脫衣舞俱樂部還沒開
Strip club's not open yet.
你去查科佩尼科的事嗎
You'll look into Kapeniak?
如果他出現  我就能找到他
If he's on the grid, I'll find him.
-送我去地鐵中心站  -不去辦公室嗎
- Drop me at metro center. - Not the office?
我要去找瑞秋
I'm gonna talk to Rachel.
她會像昨晚那樣否認一切的
She'll deny everything, like she did last night.
她不能否認上了斯坦普的車  你看到她了
She can't deny getting into Stamper's car. You saw her.
或許你可以拿篇報道她爸爸的稿子給她看
Maybe you send a version of the story, about her dad?
沒人會發表的
No one would print it.
可瑞秋不知道啊
Rachel doesn't know that.
她說"隨你便  賤人"
She said, "Go to town, bitch."
不會管用的  我得當面跟她談
It won't work. I have to get in her face.
恭喜
Congratulations.
-我們都替你高興  -謝謝
- We're thrilled for you. - Thank you.
我想親自跟鮑勃和泰瑞說
I wanted to fill in Bob and Terry personally.
我們快開始吧  我什麼時候出發去匹茲堡
Now let's get to it. I have to leave for Pittsburgh in what?
20分鐘後
20 minutes.
幫吉姆衝刺  就要到終點了
Home stretch with Jim. Whistle-stop tour.
現在形勢很好
Looking good out there.
的確  但我們還是不想冒險
Very good. But we don't want to take any chances.
接替你的黨鞭人選  弗蘭克
Now, your replacement as whip, Frank.
鮑勃已經提出了一些想法
Bob has already shared some thoughts.
我喜歡霍華德·韋伯
I like Howard Webb.
韋伯不錯  你考慮過韋斯·巴克沃特嗎
Webb is a solid choice. Have you thought about Wes Buchwalter?
巴克沃特太衝動
Buchwalter's a hot-head.
那麼韋伯你覺得可以嗎  弗蘭克
Well, could you live with Webb, Frank?
韋伯懂戰術  但做事虎頭蛇尾
Webb is a good tactician, but he lacks follow-through.
巴克沃特是個粗人
The problem with Buchwalter is he's too abrasive.
毫無魅力  樹敵太多
No charm. Lots of enemies.
還有別的選擇嗎
Is there a third option?
他們是黨團資歷最深的兩位  輪到他們了
They're the two most senior members in the caucus. It's their turn.
總統先生  可不可以讓黨內成員一起挑選
Mr. President, what if we let the caucus pick?
大家公平競爭  他們兩人都很有資質
Let it be a wide-open race. Both men are qualified.
領導層在這事上要意見一致
The leadership should be united in this.
我們不能各自支持不同的候選人  弗蘭克
We don't want to be backing different candidates, Frank.
那我們就乾脆別插手  誰都別支持誰
So we stay out of it and neither of us backs anyone.
這挺好
I like it.
黨團會尊重憑實力競爭上來的人
Caucus will respect someone who did it the old-fashioned way.
幾位  這事你們做主
Well, gentlemen, it's your call to make.
你們自己討論決定  然後告訴我
Figure it out amongst yourselves. Let me know what you decide.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
幫我接劉易斯部長
Put me through to Secretary Lewis.
弗蘭克  我不想為這事跟你爭
Frank, I don't want to go to battle with you on this.
我們犯過這種錯
We've been down that road.
說得是啊
I couldn't agree more.
公平競爭讓我緊張
An open race makes me nervous.
我只是提議一下
Well, look, it was just a suggestion.
-我再想想吧  -謝謝
- I'll put some thought into it. - Thank you.
我去做做他的工作吧
You know, let me -- let me go work on him.
祝你好運了
Good luck.
你來幹什麼
What are you doing here?
問我要點什麼
Ask me what I want to order.
想好點什麼了嗎  先生
Have you decided, sir?
你馬上辭職  告訴里昂你不幹了
I need you to quit your job. Tell Leon it's your last day.
為什麼
Why?
表現自然點
Act normal.
要什麼配菜
Did you want a side with that?
他們能找到你一次
They found you once.
不能冒險再有第二次
We can't take the chance they'll find you again.
我去哪弄錢
What am I supposed to do about money?
照我說的做  回家  收拾東西
Do as I say. Go home and pack your things.
我十點過來
I'll come by around ten.
-那我就無權決定...  -夠了
- Well -- but I don't get a say in any... - Stop it.
只收拾一個箱子
One suitcase. That's it.
-你至少也告訴我...  -我要肉餡土豆餡餅
- Can you at least tell me... - I'll take the shepherd's pie
配菜要球芽甘藍
with a side of Brussels sprouts.
帶走
To go.
我們不想上法庭  她的律師不想上法庭
We don't want a trial. Her lawyers don't want a trial.
但科爾女士就是不聽勸
But Ms. Cole won't listen to reason.
即便如此  如果你再給我點時間
That said, if you give me a little more time, I think that --
如果她想上法庭  那就隨她
If she wants to go to court, then let's give her that.
雖然她現在不肯講理  不代表將來...
Just because she's being unreasonable now doesn't mean she --
我受夠了
I'm done.
你這是膝跳反應
That's a knee-jerk reaction.
我知道你不是個不理智不耐心的人
I've never known you to be a person who was irrational or impatient.
我再去找找她的律師  或許我們...
Let me check back with her lawyers, and maybe we can --
最早什麼時候能開庭
What's the soonest we can get a trial date?
克萊爾
Claire...
給我個大致時間
Give me a timeframe.
最早也六個月後吧
Six months, at the earliest.
轉告她那邊  然後就中止溝通
Inform her people, then no more communication.
作為你的律師  我有責任強烈建議你不要這麼做
As your counsel, it is my duty to strongly advise you against this.
我明白  謝謝你  奧利弗
I understand and I thank you, Oliver.
謝謝
Thank you.
-怎麼樣  -他們不肯透露私人聯絡方式
- So? - They wouldn't give me individual contact info,
但這裏是過去三年在東非工作過的
but here's every doctor who served in east Africa
所有醫生的名單
during the last three years.
健康維護組織呢
And what about the HMO?
收取固定預付費用後  為特定地區主動參保人群提供全面醫療服務的體系
需要同意書  也在袋子裏了
You need a consent form. And it's in the packet.
私人醫師
東非
大衛·阿普博姆醫生
有事嗎
Can I help you?
我找瑞秋·波斯納
Yeah. I'm looking for Rachel Posner.
她不在
She's not here.
她晚些時候會來嗎
Uh, is she coming in later?
幹什麼
Why?
我認識她
I know her.
你朋友可把我害慘了
Well, your friend really screwed me over.
怎麼回事
What happened?
她上班上到一半就跑了
She took off, middle of her shift.
我不得不去找我的房東來幫忙
I had to put my hostess on wait staff duty.
我有點擔心  瑞秋有麻煩
Look, I'm concerned. Rachel's in real trouble.
我才不管她的私人問題呢
I don't care what her personal issues are.
我只想知道她住哪
I just need to know where she lives.
你們不是認識嗎
I thought you knew her.
我們認識  但有日子沒見了
I do. It's just been a while.
她給我發短信說她想自殘
And she sent me a text message saying she wants to hurt herself.
現在又不接電話
And now she won't answer her phone.
她有精神病史
She has a history of mental illness.
你得幫幫我啊
You've gotta help me out.
我幫不了
Look, I can't.
她的工資和稅務報表  上面的地址是個郵箱
Her W-2, the address is a P.O. Box.
有什麼都行
I'll take whatever I can get.
-我去辦公室幫你看看  -謝謝
- Let me see what I got in the office. - Thank you.
如果你找到她  叫她別回來了
If you find her, you tell her not to come back.
我才不需要瘋子來我這兒搗亂
I don't need some nutcase creating chaos in here.
-南茜  -是  先生
- Nancy? - Yes, sir?
道格回來了嗎
Is Doug back yet?
在辦公室  還有
In his office. And, sir?
我們開始收到生日賀卡了  還有幾件禮物
Birthday cards have started to arrive. A few presents.
寫感謝信  記錄禮物  貴重的...
Thank you notes. Inventory the presents. Anything valuable...
擺進會議室
Goes in the conference room?
便宜的...
Anything cheap...
給實習生
Goes to the interns.
你知道怎麼處理賀卡
And you know what to do with the cards.
當然
Yes, sir.
我今晚去接她
I'm picking her up tonight.
我在喬帕都安排好了
I got everything set up for her in Joppa.
那是哪裏
Where's that?
馬裏蘭  巴爾的摩北30分鐘路程
Maryland. About 30 minutes north of Baltimore.
太近了
That's close to home.
我們想讓她消失  但我們得能找到她
We want her to disappear, but not on us.
-好吧  一次性電話買好了嗎  -嗯
- Fine. Do you have the burner? - Yeah.
生日快樂
Happy birthday.
預付款的  你只要開機撥號就行
It's prepaid. All you need to do is turn it on and dial.
電話記錄還得處理掉
We still have the phone history.
所以日後更要小心了
All the more reason to be safe going forward.
克裏斯蒂娜怎麼樣了
Where are we with Christina?
我在辦
I'm on it.
安排她去琳達手下  我今早打過電話了
Linda's office. I called her this morning.
你是吉莉安·科爾嗎
Are you Gillian Cole?
是的  我們認識嗎
Yeah. Uh, have we met?
沒有  但你認識我丈夫
No, we haven't met. You know my husband.
你丈夫
Your husband?
大衛·阿普博姆
David Applebaum.
看來是真的嘍
So it's true.
那只是個錯誤
It was a mistake.
你想看看我們的孩子嗎  我可以給你看看照片
You want to see our kids? I can show you pictures.
阿普博姆太太  我...
Mrs. Applebaum, I -- I'm...
你以為你是誰啊
Who the fuck do you think you are?
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
你抱歉  我覺得你並不抱歉
You're sorry? I don't think you're sorry.
而且你也休想
And don't think for a second
憑這個孩子來向我們要錢
you're gonna use that baby to get money out of us.
他根本不知道我懷孕了
He doesn't even know I'm pregnant.
但你知道他是有婦之夫
But you knew he was married.
你怎麼能這樣
How could you?
-他說起過我們嗎  -沒有
- Did he talk about us? - No.
說謊的婊子  我讓你難堪了嗎
Lying bitch. Am I embarrassing you?
你想過這對我和我孩子的羞辱嗎
Did you think about how you would humiliate me and my kids?
再跟別人老公上床記得戴套
Use a condom the next time you fuck somebody's husband.
還不到24小時
It's been less than 24 hours.
她正在上班就突然辭職了
She quits her job in the middle of a shift?
她害怕了
She's scared.
換了我也會跑
I'd take off, too.
是安德伍德
It's Underwood.
他行動比我們快
He's moving faster than we are.
脫衣舞女呢
What about the stripper?
不肯開口
Refuses to talk.
科佩尼科呢
Kapeniak?
住址不詳  沒兄弟姐妹  父母雙亡
No current address. No siblings. Parents are dead.
瑞秋是唯一的機會
Rachel's the last loose end.
除了酒駕  她肯定還知道點別的
She must know something else. Bigger than the DUI.
知道她去哪了嗎
Any idea where she went?
有個杜邦的郵箱地址  但管理員都沒見過她
I got a P.O. Box in Dupont, but none of the clerks have seen her.
我可以去那裏守株待兔
I could go stake it out, but...
你找過你的人了嗎
Have you talked to your guy yet?
明後天吧
In the next day or two.
他會把羅素自殺的警方報告拿給我
He's bringing me the police report on Russo's suicide.
我盡量多套些信息
I'll press him for more.
你下一步怎麼辦
And what's your next move?
想想怎麼回復這個
Trying to figure out how to respond to this.
週一下午三點  地點你定
幾個小時前收到的
I got it a couple hours ago.
他是在給你下套
I think he's setting her up.
我知道怎麼應付他
I know how to handle him.
他知道的越少越好
The less he learns, the better.
我們也許能打探到消息
We might learn something.
是他說了算  怎麼打探
Not with him calling the shots.
地點是我定
I'm choosing the place.
有什麼區別
As if that makes a difference.
我又不會跟他上床  就是談話
I'm not gonna fuck him. Just talk to him.
我去下洗手間
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
-抱歉  我不該  -沒關係
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have -- - That's okay.
有關係
No, it's not.
我不希望你疏忽大意
I just don't want you to be careless.
不會的
I won't be.
你不想有自己的生活
You want no life?
想一個人做三個人的工作嗎
You want more work than three people can handle?
你想找個第一個月
You want a decent chance
就可能被炒的工作嗎
that you could be fired within the first month?
如果你感興趣  咱就接著談
If that tempts you, we can keep talking.
那些都不是問題
None of that intimidates me.
過去九周裏我都在管理一個選區
I've been running a congressional district for the past nine weeks
而且沒人幫我
with zero assistance.
沒人選舉我
Nobody elected me.
沒人教我怎麼做
Nobody taught me.
我那麼做是因為總得有人來做
I've done it because somebody had to.
羅素的事是個悲劇
What happened was tragic.
可我不會同情你
But you won't get sympathy from me.
我沒有時間
I don't have time for it.
我要是想博取同情  也不會到這兒來
I wouldn't be sitting here if I wanted a shoulder to cry on.
瑞秋
Rachel?
走開
Leave.
我說走開
I said leave.
收拾好了嗎
Are you packed?
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你今天沒辭職
So you didn't quit today.
辭了  可我改主意了
I did, but I changed my mind.
這事由不得你
This isn't your decision to make.
我要回去工作  繼續住這兒
I'm keeping my job and I'm keeping this apartment.
不行
No, you're not.
你答應過  會讓這些都過去
You promised you'd make all of this go away.
所以你得重新開始
And you starting over is the first --
我已經重新開始了  不想再來一次了
No, I already started over. I don't want to start over again.
我也不想你這樣
I wish you didn't have to.
滾出去
Get out.
Get out!
小點聲
Lower your voice.
我殺了你
I'll fucking kill you.
動手吧
Go ahead.
只有我能保護你  你還不明白嗎
I am the only one who can protect you. Don't you see that?
你不知道自己現在多危險
You have no idea how much danger you're in.
收拾東西吧
Start packing.
我每年都得問一句
You know I ask every year.
不過生日  像往年一樣
Nothing, as usual.
我們可以吃頓晚餐
I thought we could have dinner.
除非是去個沒人會認出我們的地方
Only if it's someplace where nobody will recognize us.
我不想誰走過來...
I don't want anyone walking up --
我是說在家  我可以做點菜
I mean at home. I'll cook something.
不要蛋糕
No cake.
不買蛋糕
不要禮物
No gifts.
不買禮物
那行  訴訟怎麼樣了
I can do that. How's the lawsuit coming?
我們不會有事的
We'll be fine.
我們打算將您的安保規模
We'd like to increase the size of your detail
增至國家元首級別  從明天開始
to full head of state status, starting tomorrow.
這可不行
Well, that won't be happening.
提前準備總是沒錯的
It's good to get a head start,
這樣等他們宣佈...
so that by the time they announce --
在我徹底失去隱私之前就剩這幾天了
These are my last few days before I never have privacy again.
我要盡量好好享受這幾天
I intend to savor these moments for as long as I can.
但是先生  出於安全考慮  我認為...
But, sir, in terms of safety, I think --
在國會表決認可我為副總統之前
Until I'm confirmed as the Vice President,
副總統一職空缺後  由總統提名  國會兩院多數票決認可  才算生效
安保問題仍是我來決定  對嗎
security is at my discretion. Is that correct?
理論上是的  但是...
Technically, yes. But --
那不就得了
Then that's settled.
那好吧  我們等正式宣佈
All right. We'll wait until the announcement.
那麼  經國會認可後
Now, assuming the confirmation goes through,
我們就要解決您搬入
we'll need to work out the logistics
海軍天文台的後勤工作
of moving you into the Naval Observatory.
天文台地界內的"天文台一號圈"為美國副總統官邸
這也不行
That won't be happening, either.
議員會繼續住在他的別墅裏
The congressman will be remaining in his townhouse.
但那裏沒有必要的安保基建
But it doesn't have the necessary security infrastructure.
那你們就去建啊
Then you'll need to build it.
要建防爆設施
We're talking blast-proofing,
固定線路通信網絡  24小時辦公室空間
hardwired communications networks, 24-hour office space --
有志者事竟成
Where there's a will, there's a way.
我會直接跟你聯絡  討論改建計劃
I'll contact you directly about setting a plan in motion.
你走之前  還有件事
And one last thing before you go.
把艾德華·密查姆安排在我的安保隊伍裏
I'd like to have Edward Meechum serve on my detail.
他是國會警察
He's Capitol Police.
目前是  你要調他去特勤處
For now. You're about to appoint him to the Secret Service.
那得經過加速培訓
That would require an accelerated training program.
先生  我們有很多合格的特工
Sir, we have plenty of qualified agents.
有男有女  都有豐富經驗
Men and women with years of experience.
我很期待與他們合作
And I look forward to working with all of them,
只要艾德華·密查姆也是安保隊一員就行
as long as Edward Meechum is on the detail.
多謝你前來
Thank you very much for your time.
謝謝你  先生
Thank you, sir.
佐伊·巴恩斯
石溪公園
弗·安德伍德
我就來
南茜  讓密查姆把車開過來
Nancy, have Meechum bring the car around.
上一次就是最後一次
You know, the last time was the last time.
我知道  但這很重要
I know. But this is important.
你總想拉我下水  我不幹了
You keep selling me that swampland. I'm done buying.
再也不幹了
No more.
掩蓋酒駕的事  你說能牽扯到巴尼·豪爾
Cover-up. You said it went as high as Barney Hull.
我不是那麼說的
That's not what I said.
你把瑞秋·波斯納的拘捕記錄給我時...
When you gave me Rachel Posner's arrest file --
我說的是  肯定有大人物干預  記錄才會消失
What I said is that arrests don't disappear without a big-ass wand.
那可不能當做證據
That ain't the same as proof.
我們認為這事牽扯到議會領導層
We think the congressional leadership took part.
我才不關心
I don't care.
不  你關心  我知道你關心的
Yes, you do. I know you do.
不  我真的不關心
No, I really don't.
當年你幫我暴露毒品...
When you helped me expose the drug --
他們不過是拿點小恩小惠的街頭黑警
They were dirty street cops stuffing a few grams in their pockets.
這事可不一樣  都是有權有勢的大人物
This is different. Powerful fucking people.
黑警就是黑警  你想保護他們嗎
Dirty cops are dirty cops. You want to protect them?
我還有養老保險和家人
I have a pension and a family.
我明白  但是...
I understand. But --
不要再聯繫我了
Don't contact me again.
死者坐在車子的副駕座上
盧卡斯·古德溫
警方報告說
羅素是在
盧卡斯·古德溫
警方報告說
副駕座上
至佐伊·巴恩斯
盧卡斯·古德溫
警方報告說
羅素是在
副駕座上
佐伊·巴恩斯
還有別的嗎
盧卡斯·古德溫
沒了
佐伊·巴恩斯
這證明不了
什麼
盧卡斯·古德溫
他怎麼
沒在正駕座上
佐伊·巴恩斯
不聊了
你的手機在哪
Where's your cell?
這裏  我沒在錄音
Here. It's not recording.
你得刪掉我們之間所有的通話記錄
I need to ask you to delete all of our phone history.
我為什麼要刪掉
Why would I do that?
我這是在保護我們兩個人
I'm trying to protect both you and I.
要坐牢的又不是我
I'm not facing prison.
他酒駕不是你替他掩蓋的嗎
You didn't cover up the arrest?
是不是因為你想讓他競選州長
Is it because you wanted him to be governor?
不是  他惹了麻煩  我就伸了援手
No. He was in trouble, so I helped.
之後他表現出參選意願  我就提供了指導
And later he expressed a desire to run, and I offered guidance.
指導一個酒鬼嗎
To an alcoholic?
他當時戒了酒  正在恢復中
To a sober recovering alcoholic.
你是指望他會自毀前程嗎
Did you want him to self-sabotage?
當然不是
Absolutely not.
他沒戲了  馬修斯才來參選
It got Matthews in the race.
我願意支持有上進心的人
I like to back people who want to succeed.
比如說你自己
Take yourself as an example.
你不過是漁翁得利
You just took advantage of the situation.
得利的是馬修斯  我沒指望能當副總統啊
Matthews took advantage. I didn't seek the nomination.
羅素死的時候坐在副駕座上
Russo was in the passenger seat when he died.
這話不準確
That's not entirely accurate.
我看過警方報告
I saw the police report.
我還直接和警局局長談過呢
And I spoke to the commissioner directly,
因為我關心彼得  我想瞭解全部細節
because I cared about Peter and I wanted to know the full story.
那他沒坐在副駕座上嗎
He wasn't in the passenger seat?
副駕座的車門開著  他半邊身子躺在外面
The passenger door was open, and he was halfway out.
警方認為
They think that...
他可能中途後悔了
he might have had second thoughts.
如果我去問巴尼·豪爾  他會證實你的話嗎
If I speak to Barney Hull, he'll confirm that?
你什麼意思  佐伊
What are you suggesting, Zoe?
也許有人謀殺了他
Maybe there was foul play.
要是有任何謀殺的跡象
If there was a hint of foul play,
你覺得警方會不去調查嗎
don't you think the police would have investigated?
就這些掩蓋他酒駕的警察嗎
The same police that buried his DUI?
你認為我也脫不了干係
And you think I was involved.
你們之間有聯繫
There's a connection between you.
聽聽你在說什麼  荒唐至極
listen to you. You sound ludicrous.
我只是問問而已
I'm just asking questions.
不  你這是在瞎猜  瞎聯繫
No, you're connecting dots that don't exist.
你想讓我別插手  裝作什麼都不知道
You want me to just walk away? Act as if I don't know anything?
沒錯  是我替彼得解了圍
Yes, I got Peter out of a jam.
沒錯  我讓他去找科佩尼科
Yes, I sent him to speak to Kapeniak.
但除此之外  就沒別的了
But beyond that, there's nothing to know.
別怪我  但現在我實在沒法相信你的話
Can you blame me if I find it difficult to trust you right now?
信不信隨你
Trust me or not,
我很快就要獲得認可正式成為副總統了
but I'm about to be confirmed as the vice president.
我們的合作關係已經延伸到總統層面了
And our relationship extends to the Oval Office now.
別無緣無故地沒事找事
Don't step out of the sunlight for no reason.
讓我們忘記過去  展開新的合作
Let's start this new chapter with a clean slate.
你回去好好想想  我會聯繫你
Now you sleep on that, and I'll be in touch.
我們先做血液和激素檢測
We'll start with blood and hormone tests.
結果幾天之內就能出來
Those results should be back within a few days.
如果結果不錯
If they're good,
我們就開始對你和你丈夫進行基因檢測
we'll move on to genetic testing for both you and your husband.
你和他談過了嗎
Have you spoken to him yet?
還沒有  我想先做檢測
Not yet. I want to do the tests first.
這周什麼時間做都可以
We can do those anytime this week.
我會讓我的人跟你這邊聯絡
I'll have my office call yours.
差點忘了
I almost forgot.
我上網做了些研究
I've been doing some research on the Internet.
網上的話不能都信啊
Be careful of the Internet.
我在搜索四十歲以上孕婦的
Well, I was looking into common issues
孕期常見問題時
associated with post-40 pregnancies,
查到了一個藥物
and this drug came up.
但沒查到什麼詳細信息  它叫靜脈
But there wasn't much on it. It's Cruvenae...
靜脈雌酮
Cruvenae-tenuestrin.
你沒找到詳細信息是因為這種藥
You probably haven't found much because it's,
還處在測試階段
still in the beta stage.
這藥物有什麼療效
And what does it do?
它能促進血液流往胎盤
It helps maximize blood flow to the placenta.
此前還沒有哪種藥物能做到這一點
Until CVT there hasn't been any viable drug for that.
這藥目前仍有爭議
The jury's still out.
但是各年齡段的女性都可能患上胎盤機能不全
But placental insufficiency affects women of all ages.
你現在先別擔心這個
I wouldn't worry about it for now.
我們還是按部就班  慢慢來
That's putting the cart way before the horse.
馬修斯已經穩操勝券
You know, Matthews has this locked up,
但是國會保守人士認為
but conservatives on the hill are saying
他這次重回州長之位  還會像從前一樣
he's gonna return to Harrisburg with the same myopic,
目光短淺  增加赤字
deficit-growing mentality.
至於馬修斯獲勝後接任副總統的人選
Now, as to who's gonna replace Matthews when he wins...
我把牆燈關上不礙事吧
Can I at least turn off the overhead?
當然沒事
Of course.
...還能有誰在財政上更恣意妄為...
...someone even more fiscally irresponsible...
需要我去樓下工作嗎
Do you want me to go work downstairs?
不用  沒事  給我騰個地方就行
No. That's fine. Just make some room.
你還沒表態呢
You haven't said a word.
是的
No.
那我們怎麼辦
Where does that leave us?
我完全準備好了
I'm fully prepared.
早就蓄勢待發了
And I have been for some time.
我知道你會做出你認為最好的決定
I know you'll do whatever you think is best.
但是安德伍德確認了
But Underwood confirmed it.
他將被提名為副總統
He's gonna be tapped for VP.
那對我們一點幫助也沒有
That doesn't get us any closer.
我們知道羅素的死給馬修斯掃清了障礙
Well, we know that Russo cleared the way for Matthews.
只能印證理論  但不是證據
It reinforces the theory. It doesn't give us proof.
我們不能指責他耍卑鄙手段
We can't go after the guy for playing dirty.
那根本不算新聞
That's not news.
國會裏一半的混蛋都在耍手段
Half the fuckers in Congress play dirty.
他扶持一個假候選人  就為到時搞垮他
He propped up a sham candidate, just to take him down.
那天晚上沒人強迫羅素喝酒
Nobody forced Russo to drink that night.
那傢伙本來就是個酒鬼
The guy was an alcoholic.
好吧  除了三天後他自殺了
Okay, we don't know what happened that night,
關於那晚我們一無所知
other than three days later he killed himself.
你還會再聯繫他嗎
Are you gonna contact him again?
我不知道
I don't know.
我們得放慢進度  退一步重新考慮
We need to slow down, take a step back, and reevaluate.
我們已經讓瑞秋溜走了
We already let Rachel slip away.
除非掌握更多信息  否則都是徒勞
There's no point until we have more.
我們應該讓他去猜  而不是
We should keep him guessing, not --
等等  從哪裏打探更多信息  從誰那裏
Wait-- have more from where? From who?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我們應該先嘗試別的辦法
But we should exhaust all options
-再考慮讓佐伊去聯繫安德伍德  -但我們別無選擇
- before Zoe reaches back out to Underwood. - But we don't have any options.
-那會顯得我們別無選擇  -我們已經撞南牆了
- It looks desperate. - We are up against a brick wall.
除非安德伍德
And unless Underwood--
佐伊
Zoe...?
我需要一個人想想
I just need to think.
大家一起討論吧
Well, let's think about it together.
明天給你打電話
I'll call you tomorrow.
弗萊迪
Freddy?
怎麼了  弗蘭克
Yeah, Frank?
今早的肋排是不是有什麼不同
Was there something different about these ribs this morning?
更好吃了還是難吃了
Better or worse?
我本以為你的肋排是美味到極致了
I didn't think that they could get any better,
不過今天的真是不同凡響
but these were something special.
換了一個新屠夫
Well, tried a new butcher.
他慢慢地給豬放血
Slow-bleeds his hogs.
這屠宰方法不合法  但是...
It ain't legal, but...
我不會告訴別人的
Well, I won't tell anyone.
我不知道還會不會再去他那裏買肉
I don't know if I'm gonna go back to him.
我去他的店
Went out to his shop.
店後有個房間
He's got a room in the back
他就在那裏殺豬
where he does it.
房間是隔音的  裏面裝備齊全
Soundproof. A whole setup.
為什麼要弄成隔音的
W-- why soundproof?
因為豬叫得太厲害
'Cause of how they scream.
它們能嗅到死神來臨的氣息
They can smell it coming.
往它們的喉嚨裏插根管子
You stick that pipe in their throat,
接下來的十分鐘簡直生不如死
the next 10 minutes is hell.
你的鼓膜都能被震破
Bust your fucking eardrums.
人性化的方式是速戰速決
Now, the humane way to do it is to make it quick.
裝作餵食那樣提一桶泔水來  然後  砰
Bring out a bucket of slop like it's feeding time and -- -- bam.
對準後腦勺來上一鍬
Shovel right to the base of the head.
豬一聲也不會吭
No screaming.
博奇同意公開競爭  但他說的很清楚
He's willing to open up the race, but Birch was very clear:
如果他不能支持誰  你也不行
if he can't endorse anyone, you can't either.
很公平
That's fair.
你真的希望巴克沃特勝選
You really want Buchwalter to win?
我希望最優秀的人能勝選
I want the best man to win.
謹小慎微的廢話  說了等於沒說
That sounds like a cagey bullshit non-answer to me.
我不想插手這件事  泰瑞
I'm on the sidelines for this one, Terry.
什麼事你不插手  弗蘭克
You're never on the sidelines, Frank.
回頭見
I'll see you around.
未知號碼
我們能重新開始了嗎
克萊爾  你不回我電話
Claire. You wouldn't return my calls.
我就回來
I'll be back.
我的律師說我不應該再和你接觸
My attorney said that I shouldn't be in contact with you.
藍十字會告訴我保險被取消了
Blue Cross said my insurance was canceled.
為會員及其家屬提供住院等醫療保險的非贏利組織
解雇金條款裏規定了一年的健康保險
The severance package gave me health coverage for up to a year.
好像是的
That sounds right.
所以肯定出了什麼問題
So there must be some kind of mistake.
你得去跟保險公司說啊
Well, you'll have to talk to the insurance company.
我去了  他們說保險被終止了
I did. They said it was terminated.
如果僱主不同意  他們就無法恢復
They can't reinstate it without the employer's approval.
你想讓我幫你一把
And you want me to get involved?
有一些我需要的藥物
There's medication that I need
必須通過健康維護組織獲取
that I can't get unless it goes through my HMO.
這我知道  我看過你的檔案
I'm well aware. I-- I reviewed your records.
-什麼  -你簽了同意書
- What? - You signed a consent form.
不  我沒有
No. I-- I-- I didn't.
你偽造了我的簽名嗎
You forged my signature?
阿普博姆太太是不是去找過你
Did a Mrs. Applebaum pay you a visit?
你知道你這麼做是...
You realize what you're doing is--
民事罪  不是刑事
Civil. Not criminal.
你想清楚了嗎  因為等我們上了法庭
Have you thought this out? Because when we go to court--
六個月後嗎
You mean six months from now?
你還有四個月就生了  不是嗎
You're expecting in four, no?
那麼你這四個月就沒有藥物可用
That's four months without the medicine you need.
如果有必要的話  我寧願讓你的孩子
I'm wiling to let your child wither and die inside you
夭折在你肚子裏
if that's what's required.
但我們都不想看到那種結果
But neither of us wants that.
說說看  你真想和我做敵人嗎
Now tell me, am I really the sort of enemy you want to make?
但你還有選擇
But here's the alternative.
這家機構  這些員工
This office, this staff,
一年兩千兩百萬美元都給你
22 million a year could be yours.
淨水計劃也是你的
The CWI could be yours.
你我的恩怨一筆勾銷
And you and me, we wash our hands of each other.
你想收買我
You're trying to buy me.
不  我們初見時我答應給你權力
No. When we first met, I promised to empower you.
我這是在兌現諾言
I'm fulfilling that promise.
你騙我怎麼辦
How do I get screwed?
不會的  我辭職  你取代我的職位
You don't. I resign. You take my place.
沒其他條件嗎
No strings?
沒有
None.
民調顯示吉姆·馬修斯
Exit polls have Jim Matthews winning
將以9到12個百分點的絕對優勢贏得競選
by anywhere from a nine-to-twelve-percent margin of victory.
喂
Hello?
安德伍德太太嗎
Mrs. Underwood?
我是
Yes.
你好  這裏是拉森醫生辦公室
Hi. I'm calling from Dr. Larson's office
跟您確認一下明早十點的血檢和尿檢
to confirm your 10 a.m. tomorrow for the blood and urine tests.
我去不了
I can't come.
如果明天不行
Well, if tomorrow doesn't work,
我們可以重新安排到週四  甚至週一
we can reschedule for Thursday or even Monday--
不  別給我安排了
No, I won't be rescheduling.
請替我感謝拉森醫生的會診
Please tell Dr. Larson I appreciate all her consultation,
但我經過再三考慮
but I've put a great deal of thought into this
決定不再進行其他檢測了
and I won't be pursuing any further tests.
謝謝
Thank you.
你考慮過我們之前討論的事了嗎
Have you thought about what we discussed?
你說得沒錯  我們是該拋開過去  重新開始
I think you're right. We should start with a clean slate.
我們的短信呢
What about our text messages?
弗·安德伍德
全部刪除
還有通訊錄
And the contact?
弗·安德伍德
刪除
我們之間沒事吧
Are we good?
沒事
Yeah.
我們忘記這些亂七八糟的事
And we can put all this other nonsense behind us
互相信任  互相幫助  可以嗎
and trust one another and continue to help one another?
這樣很好
I'd like that.
那現在算是拋開過去了
Then consider the slate clean.
回答我個問題
Answer me one thing.
副駕座的事
The passenger seat.
你說羅素是想出去
You said Russo was trying to get out.
這沒什麼奇...
That there was nothing ab--
我們不是剛剛說好...
I thought we just agreed to--
我想相信你  但你得說明白
I want to believe you, but I need details.
你有所隱瞞
More than what you're sharing.
你想問什麼
What's your question?
羅素酒癮復發當晚  他出席了一個募捐活動
The night Russo fell off the wagon he was at a fundraiser.
麥克奈利癌癥研究所...
The McNeally Cancer Institute--
警察報告裏全都有
All in the police report.
瑞秋·波斯納當晚也在那家酒店
Rachel Posner was at the hotel that night.
那是誰
Who's that?
羅素被捕時跟他在一起的應召女
The call girl who was with Russo when he was arrested.
我又不知道她叫什麼
I didn't know her name.
她消失了  弗蘭西斯
She disappeared, Francis.
什麼時候
When?
別裝不知道  我給行李員看了張照片
Don't act surprised. I showed the bellmen a photo.
其中一個記得見過她
One of them remembers seeing her.
她是個妓女
The girl's a prostitute.
她肯定經常出現在各種酒店
I'm sure she frequents many hotels.
可偏巧那晚去那家酒店嗎
But that hotel on that night?
你這語氣像斯克斯基女士似的
Well, now you sound like Ms. Skorsky talking.
我沒和任何人說過這事
I haven't discussed this with anyone.
我想先問你
I wanted to ask you first.
我不知道那晚發生了什麼
I have no idea what happened that night,
只知道彼得又開始酗酒
except that Peter started drinking again.
我不知道有誰在場
I don't know who was or wasn't there.
真希望我在
I wish I was.
說不定我能阻止他
Maybe I could have stopped him.
你知道瑞秋在哪嗎
Do you know where Rachel is?
相信我的話
Listen to what I am saying.
我是想要保護我們兩個人
I am trying to protect us both.
誰都有可能問這些問題
These are questions anyone could ask.
但現在只有你在問
But no one is, except you.
我真不知你想幹什麼
I can't imagine what you're after.
我冒了個險
I took a chance.
跑去你家  任你擺佈
Showed up at your house and placed myself at your feet.
於公於私都跨過了道德底線
Crossed ethical lines, professionally, physically.
我願意為這些事負責
And I hold myself accountable for that.
這都是我的選擇  我願承擔後果
Those were my choices, and I can live with them.
我也希望向前看
I'd like to move forward,
但我需要知道我到底捲入了什麼事
but I need to know exactly what I was a part of. That...
我要確定我沒有捲入...
that I wasn't a part of someone's...
把話說完
Finish your thought.
一起謀殺
Part of someone's murder.
天哪
Jesus.
我想要相信你  弗蘭西斯
I want to believe you, Francis.
我知道你
I know you --
簡寧
Janine!
快進來
Come in.
我打不通你電話
I've been calling you.
進屋坐吧
Come in. Sit down.
喝點什麼嗎
Um, you -- you want something?
水  或者果汁
Some, uh, water or, um, juice?
你要出門
You going somewhere?
你要去哪
Hey. You going somewhere?
去我媽媽那裏  在伊薩卡
To my mom's. In Ithaca.
-什麼  -我要走了
- What? - I'm leaving.
不不  不行
No. No, no, no. No. No way.
-我們什麼都沒有  -你要放棄嗎
- We have nothing. - Are you giving up on this?
這世上只有三個人知道他幹了什麼
There are only three people in the world that know what he has done,
其中一個已經死了
and one of them is gone.
如果我們有證據  盧卡斯
If we had anything, Lucas,
任何確鑿證據
any hard evidence
哪怕是一個願意公開的信息源
or even a fucking quote from a source that would go on record for us,
那也好說
that would be one thing.
可我們純粹在捕風捉影  而他不是鬧著玩的
But we are grasping, and he is not fucking around.
是你說服佐伊追查這事的
You were the one who told Zoe to pursue this.
她告訴了我你說的話
She told me what you said.
能把你嚇壞的文章才是真正重要的
The only stories that mattered were the ones that scared you to death.
這可不僅僅是死亡威脅
Okay, this isn't just death threats.
這是來真的
This is real.
他不知道你  但他知道我
He doesn't know about you, but he knows about me.
這是在我郵箱裏發現的
These were in my mailbox.
沒有發信地址
No return address.
他照了她的照片
He took these of her?
還能是誰  你留著吧
Who else? You can keep them.
但我不認為這對你有什麼幫助
But I don't think they're gonna help you.
我們必須阻止他
We need to stop him.
變態混蛋
Sick fucking shit.
簡寧  你不能就這麼逃跑
Janine, you cannot run away from this!
我這一輩子從來都找硬骨頭啃
My entire career, I have always chosen the tough stories.
我一向無所畏懼
I have been fearless.
可你猜怎麼著
But you know what?
我這回真的害怕極了
I'm really fucking scared this time.
他重權在握
He's got power.
他輸不起
He's got a lot to lose.
現在他完全佔了上風
And right now he is winning.
拜託  我需要你幫助  別這樣
Please, I need your help. Please, don't do this.
別做夢了  盧卡斯
Just wake the fuck up, Lucas!
事故發生於昨晚八點左右
The incident occurred at approximately eight p.m. last night
在大教堂高地地鐵站北向的列車軌道上
on the northbound tracks of the Cathedral Heights metro station.
華盛頓特區警察已經判定是一起意外
D.C. Police have ruled the death an accident.
佐伊·巴恩斯
地鐵悲劇
新聞界對事故表示哀悼
佐伊·巴恩斯是頭條網的資深撰稿人
Zoe Barnes was a senior contributor at slugline.com.
佐伊·巴恩斯
地鐵悲劇
新聞界對事故表示哀悼
此前她曾在《華盛頓先驅報》
Previously she worked at the Washington Herald
做都市新聞記者和政治記者
as a metro reporter and political correspondent.
巴恩斯報道過多條重要新聞
Barnes broke several major stories,
包括教育改革法案的草案
include an early draft of the Education Reform and Achievement Act,
以及導致邁克爾·科恩參議員
as well as a college newspaper article
未能被提名國務卿的
that derailed Senator Michael Kern's
一篇公報社論
nomination for Secretary of State...
你覺得那些文件怎麼樣
What'd you think of the files?
有不少可以下手的地方
There's plenty to work with.
你看了自己的嗎
Did you look at your own?
裏面什麼都沒有
There was nothing there.
裏面該有什麼嗎
Should there be?
不應該
No.
即便你在撒謊
Even if you're lying,
但我現在什麼也沒找到
the fact that I haven't been able to find anything
這說明你很擅長隱藏蹤跡
tells me you're very good at covering your tracks.
這點對我來說很寶貴  這裏就是我們的戰場
That's, uh, valuable to me. Here's our battleground.
113票
113 votes.
看來你已經掌握大致情況了
You have the skeletons.
如果我失敗了  他們不會放過我
If I lose, they'll come after me.
這是你必須承擔的風險
That's a risk you have to take.
我怎麼知道你不是在利用我
How do I know you're not just using me?
為別人競選製造障礙
Throwing a wrench into someone else's bid?
那是另一種風險  你也可以選擇等上十年
That's another risk. The alternative is you wait 10 years.
你選我肯定是有原因的
You chose me for a reason.
我想知道是什麼
I'd like to know what it is.
好吧
All right.
你發起過多少次導彈攻擊
How many missile strikes did you launch?
多到讓我整夜不能安睡
Enough to keep me awake at night.
但你還是那麼做了
But you did it anyway.
是的  沒錯
Yes, I did.
會傷及多少婦女兒童
How many women and children?
太多了
Too many.
就算知道會傷及無辜
And you launched those missiles
你還是義無反顧地發射了導彈
knowing all those innocent people would die.
我是奉命殲滅敵人
I had orders to eliminate the enemy.
而你專業高效地完成了任務
Which you carried out expertly and efficiently.
你殺過人嗎
Have you ever killed anyone?
沒有
No.
我曾親眼目睹整棟大樓  整個村莊蕩然無存
I watched apartment buildings, entire villages gone,
就像不曾存在過
like they were never there.
如果可以  我不想再談這個話題了
I'd prefer not to talk about it, if that's all right.
你完成需要完成的任務
You did what needed to be done,
這就是我選擇你的原因  傑姬
and that's why I chose you, Jackie.
服役背景  歷史清白
Service background. Clean history.
上相  我全都看好
Photogenic. The whole package.
但更重要的是
But more importantly,
堅決  務實
ruthless pragmatism.
我們能合作嗎
Are we working together or not?
有公開或私下表示支持巴克沃特的嗎
Any public or private endorsements for Buchwalter,
我支持韋伯
I come out for Webb.
我不參與爭論  我向你保證
I'll stay out of the fray. I give you my word.
你也一樣  泰瑞
Same goes for you, Terry.
謝謝  克裏斯蒂娜
Thank you, Christina.
先生們
Gentlemen.
總統先生  賓州情況怎麼樣
Mr. President. How was Pennsylvania?
喜歡印度菜嗎
You like Indian?
先生  我看到新聞了
Sir? I've seen the news.
我知道她跟您很親近
I know she was close to you.
可怕的悲劇啊
Terrible tragedy.
今天特別探員洛克蘭來找過我  先生
Spoke to Special Agent Rockland today, sir.
我下周開始培訓
I begin my training next week.
很好
Very good.
我知道已經晚了一天
I know it's a day late.
但願這樣不失妥當
Hope it isn't inappropriate,
我想給您這個
but I wanted to give you this.
謝謝  密查姆
Thank you, Meechum.
艾德華真是太貼心了
That was very nice of Edward.
他不該為我花這種錢
He shouldn't have spent this sorta money on me.
我在樓下開了酒
I've opened some wine downstairs.
我就下去
I'll be down in a minute.
你以為我把你忘了嗎
Did you think I'd forgotten you?
也許你希望我已經忘了
Perhaps you hoped I had.
別浪費時間哀悼巴恩斯小姐了
Don't waste a breath mourning Ms. Barnes.
每只小貓都會長大
Every kitten grows up to be a cat.
一開始看起來都很無害
They seem so harmless at first.
幼小  安靜  舔著淺盤裏的牛奶
Small, quiet, lapping up their saucer of milk.
但爪子一旦長長了  貓就會撓人
But once their claws get long enough, they draw blood.
有時甚至會撓養貓人的手
Sometimes from the hand that feeds them.
對於我們這些爬向食物鏈頂端的人來說
For those of us climbing to the top of the food chain,
決不能心慈手軟
there can be no mercy.
只有一條規則  不做獵人  便為獵物
There is but one rule: hunt or be hunted.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
弗蘭克見傑姬時  牆上的著名照片中的兩人分別是
美國第36任總統林登·約翰遜[左]和理查德·拉塞爾[右]
拉塞爾是佐治亞州參議員
曾一度被認為是林登·約翰遜政治上的導師和引路人之一
但約翰遜擔任總統後  拉塞爾在《民權法案》問題上與約翰遜對立
而約翰遜為推動法案通過  對拉塞爾毫不留情
約翰遜被認為是美國近代歷史上最會耍弄權術的總統和政客
為達目的無所不用其極
但同時也被認為是美國歷史上最偉大的總統之一
在任上通過了《民權法案》  建立晚年醫保制度
完善美國社會保障體系  為美國社會進步做出巨大貢獻
在第一季中
弗蘭克辦公室桌上便放了一本新出版的約翰遜傳記
《通往權力之路》
美國第35任總統肯尼迪在達拉斯被槍手刺殺
2小時8分鐘後  副總統約翰遜接任肯尼迪的職務
成為美國第36任總統